Finding Aid to the Margaret Sanger papers SSC.MS.00138
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VIII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS, 1935-1993
  This series is equally divided between a small sampling of contemporary recordings and film footage of Sanger and documentaries made after her death. The Sound recordings subseries is arranged chronologically and consists of record album, reel-to-reel tape, and cassette tape formats. Most items have been reformatted for research use (these are noted in the Contents list). There are recordings of Sanger speeches and interviews and one made after Sanger's death of Elizabeth Bacon and Leighton Rollins discussing Sanger's last years. Films and videotapes include copies of four documentaries and two contemporary films of Sanger.
  - Sound recordings-originals, do not use
    - M. Sanger, "Family Planning," WABC New York, April 11, 1935 (2 records) (Box 110)
    - Town Hall Award to Margaret Sanger, WQXR, January 15, 1937 (10 records) (Box 110)
    - M. Sanger, "Why Birth Control Is Needed," studio recording, June 28, 1937 (3 records) (Box 110)
    - Dorothy Gordon and M. Sanger, tribute to Havelock Ellis, "Let's Talk It Over" (tribute to Havelock Ellis), WEAF, July 17, 1939 (2 records) (Box 110)
    - Fourth International Conference on Planned Parenthood, Stockholm, 1953 (3 cassette tapes) (Box 110)
    - M. Sanger and Leighton Rollins, "Portrait in Speech," October 1, 1958 (1 reel-to-reel tape) (Box 110)
    - Richard, Olive Byrne, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, 25 Nov 1977 (1 audiocassette) (Box 110A)
    - Ivins, Nancy Sanger and Margaret Sanger Marston, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, 1977 (2 audiocassettes) (Box 110A)
    - Sanger, Grant, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, 28 Mar 1977 (2 audiocassettes) (Box 110A)
    - M. Sanger, "Why Birth Control Is Needed," studio recording, June 28, 1937 (cd preservation master) (Box 110A)
  - Films and videotapes-preservation masters, do not use (Box 110A)
    - "Margaret Sanger on Birth Control," January 1928. Copyright: Fox Movietone News (VHS preservation master) (Box 110A)
    - "The Mike Wallace Interview," Sept. 24, 1957. Copyright: CBS News (1 VHS and 1 DVD preservation master) (Box 110A)
    - "The Woman Rebel Margaret Sanger," WGBH, Boston (NOVA program #316), undated (1 VHS) (Box 110A)
  - Films and videotapes-preservation masters, do not use (Box 110A)
    - Reed, Miriam, "Margaret Sanger: 1916" (one-woman show), Santa Barbara Planned Parenthood, 1993 (1 VHS) (Box 110A)
    - "Margaret Sanger," narrated by Katherine Hepburn. Copyright: Planned Parenthood World Federation (1VHS) (Box 110A)
    - "Margaret Sanger: A Public Nuisance" (produced by the Margaret Sanger Papers Project), 1992 (1 VHS) (Box 110A)
  - Sound recordings-research copies (Box 110A)
    - Richard, Olive Byrne, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, November 25, 1977 (1 audiocassette) (Box 110B)
    - Ivins, Nancy Sanger and Margaret Sanger Marston, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, 1977 (2 audiocassettes) (Box 110B)
    - Sanger, Grant, interview by Jacqueline Van Voris, March 28, 1977 (2 audiocassettes) (Box 110B)
    - Town Hall Award to Margaret Sanger, WQXR, January 15, 1937 (1 audiocassette) (Box 110B)
    - M. Sanger, "Why Birth Control Is Needed," studio recording, June 28, 1937 and Dorothy Gordon and M. Sanger, tribute to Havelock Ellis, "Let's Talk It Over" (tribute to Havelock Ellis), WEAF, July 17, 1939 (1 audiocassette and 1 cd) (Box 110B)
    - M. Sanger and Leighton Rollins, "Portrait in Speech," October 1, 1958 and M. Sanger, "Family Planning," WABC New York, April 11, 1935 (1 audiocassette) (Box 110B)
    - Fourth International Conference on Planned Parenthood, Stockholm, 1953 (1 audiocassette) (Box 110B)
  - Films and videotapes-research copies (Box 110B)
    - "Margaret Sanger," narrated by Katherine Hepburn. Copyright: Planned Parenthood World Federation (1 dvd) (Box 111)
    - "The Mike Wallace Interview," Sept. 24, 1957. Copyright: CBS News (2 VHS and 3 DVDs) Films and videotapes-research copies (Box 111)
    - "Margaret Sanger on Birth Control," January 1928. Copyright: Fox Movietone News (VHS) (Box 111)
    - Home movies (video compilation of 3 8mm films owned by Alex Sanger): 1) Slee family in Paris, circa 1932 (?); 2) J.N.H. Slee, Cape Cod, Dr. Pierson, Eliz. Newman and grandchildren of J.N.H. Slee; and 3) M. Sanger in Tucson at X-mas, Tennis, and Stuart, Grant, and Edwina Sanger (1 VHS, also available as digital file) (Box 111)
- SERIES IX. PHOTOGRAPHS, 1850-1966
  The photographs are divided into the following subseries: Margaret (Higgins) Sanger--alone (arranged chronologically); Family (subdivided into files for "Higgins," "Sanger," "Slee," and "Family dogs" and arranged alphabetically within those subdivisions); Friends and associates (divided into individuals and groups); Sites and scenes; and Miscellaneous.
  The Friends and associates subseries includes many "notables," such as Pearl Buck, Havelock Ellis, Mohandas Gandhi, Shidzue Kato, and many others. Box 112 contains photocopies for research purposes.
  See also SERIES X. OVERSIZE MATERIALS and APPENDIX: PHOTOGRAPHS LOCATED IN OTHER SERIES.
  - Photocopies (Box 112)
    Please use these for research
  - Margaret (Higgins) Sanger--alone
    - 1892-95 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - 1898-99 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - In nurse's uniform, 1899-1902 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Undated, pre-1900 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - 1900-10 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - 1911-15 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - 1916-19 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - 1920-24 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - 1925-29 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Undated, 1901-29 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - 1930-34 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - 1935-39 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - 1940-44 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - 1945-49 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Undated, 1930-49 (Box 113, Folder 15-17)
    - 1950-55 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - 1956-57 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - 1958-66 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Undated, 1950-66 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Photographic reproductions of busts & paintings of Sanger (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Family
    - Higgins
      - Anne (Purcell) Higgins (mother), 1850, n.d., and William Purcell, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 1)
      - Michael H. Higgins (father), 1925; undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - Anna (Nan) Higgins (sister), 1889-97; 1918; 1944; undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - Mary Higgins (sister), 1889-96; undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
        [see also framed photo of Mary Higgins in SERIES X. OVERSIZE, box 130]
      - Richard Higgins (brother) and family, 1937-58; undated (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - Robert Higgins (brother) and family, 1918; 1932; 1941; 1948; undated (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Thomas Higgins (brother), 1895 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - Groups, 1910; 1918; undated (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Sanger
      - William Sanger (first husband), undated (Box 115, Folder 1-2)
      - Photographic reproductions of paintings by William Sanger, 1922; undated (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - William Sanger: Ancestors and relatives, including his parents, 1889-1945; undated (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - Alexander Sanger (grandson), undated (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Grant Sanger (son), 1915-22; undated (Box 115, Folder 6-7)
      - Grant and Edwina Sanger family, 1937-56; undated (Box 115, Folder 8-9)
      - Grant and Edwina Sanger family with Margaret Sanger, 1943-56 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      - Peggy Sanger (daughter), 1912; 1915; undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - Stuart Sanger (son), 1924-33; undated (Box 115, Folder 12)
        [see also photograph of Stuart and Yale class of 1928 in Flat file]
      - Stuart and Barbara Sanger family, 1940-65 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      - Stuart and Barbara Sanger family with Margaret Sanger, 1941; 1948; undated (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - Family groups
        - Stuart, Grant and Peggy Sanger, pre-1920 (Box 115, Folder 15-16)
        - Margaret and William Sanger with children, pre-1920 (Box 115, Folder 17)
        - 1920-37 (Box 115, Folder 18-19)
    - Slee
      - J. Noah H. Slee (second husband), 1870s; 1922-40; undated (Box 115, Folder 20-21)
      - J. Noah H. Slee and Margaret Sanger, 1920s; 1924-40; undated (Box 115, Folder 22)
        [see also oversize photo of Margaret Sanger and J. Noah H. Slee in Potsdam in Flat file]
      - Slee grandchildren, including Margaret Sanger and J. Noah H. Slee, 1928-47; undated (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Dogs, undated (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Friends and associates
    See also APPENDIX: PHOTOGRAPHS LOCATED IN OTHER SERIES.
    - Individuals (including Margaret Sanger with individuals)
      - Albertson, Corey, undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
      - A-C, 1915-52; undated (Box 116, Folder 2)
      - Buck, Pearl, 1935 (Box 116)
      - Comstock, Anthony, undated (Box 116)
      - D-E, 1947-61; undated (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - Ellis, Havelock and Edith, 1918-27; undated (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - F-H, 1917-37; undated (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - Gandhi, Mohandas K. and Indira, 1959; undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - Hastings, Daniel, undated (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - I-L, 1875-80; 1916-46; undated (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - Kato, Shidzue (formerly the Baroness Ishimoto), 1922-59; undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
        [see also Groups--Japan]
      - "Marharishi" (of India), undated (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - M-N, 1925-55; undated (Box 116, Folder 11)
      - McCormick, Ada, undated (Box 116)
      - Merion, Kitty, 1925 (Box 116)
      - Nehru, Jawaharlal (also Lady Rama Rau), 1959 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - P-R, 1940; 1954; undated (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - Pandit, Mme. Vijaya Lakshmi, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 14)
      - Pierce, Walter, 1934 (Box 116, Folder 15)
      - Rose, Florence, 1957; 1960; 1966 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      - S-T, 1914; 1948; 1954; undated (Box 116, Folder 17)
      - Selincourt, Hugh de, 1925; 1927; undated (Box 116, Folder 18)
      - Stone, Abraham, 1952; 1959; undated (Box 116, Folder 19)
      - U-Z, 1952-59 (Box 116, Folder 20)
      - Unidentified, 1942; 1945-48; undated (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Groups--chronological (including Margaret Sanger)
      - (including Margaret Sanger & nursing class), Pre-1900 (Box 116, Folder 22)
      - (including Otis Skinner, H.G. Wells), 1901-19 (Box 116, Folder 23)
      - (including Dorothy Booker, Pearl Buck, Katharine (Houghton) Hepburn, Mrs. Philip Hughes, Anne Kennedy, John M. Keynes, Charles Scribner, Hugh de Selincourt), 1920-39 (Box 116, Folder 24)
      - (including Florence Rose, Stuart Sanger), 1940-49 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - (including Dorothy Brush, Abraham Stone, Ellen Watumull), 1950-66 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      - (including Dorothy Brush, Katharine (Houghton) Hepburn, Mary Hughston, Ada McCormick, Florence Rose, Hugh de Selincourt, H.G. Wells), Undated (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Groups--activities (including Margaret Sanger)
      - Trial, 1916-17 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Scenes from film "Birth Control", 1917 (Box 117, Folder 5)
      - Sanger at Smith College receiving honorary degree, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - Japan
        - Shidzue Kato, Reiko Mitsui, Dorothy Brush, and others, 1922; 1932; 1937 (Box 117, Folder 7)
        - Dorothy Brush, Shidzue Kato, Abraham Stone, and others, 1952; 1954 (Box 117, Folder 8)
        - Dorothy Brush, Shidzue Kato, Governor of Tokyo, and the 6th International Conference on Planned Parenthood, 1958-59; undated (Box 117, Folder 9-11)
          [see also photo album of Japan trip, 1959, in SERIES X. OVERSIZE]
      - India (including Dorothy Brush, Lady Rama Rau, Abraham Stone), 1952 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Sites and scenes
    - Brownsville Clinic at 46 Amboy Street, 1916 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous birth control related scenes, 1889; 1912; undated (Box 117, Folder 14-15)
    - Sanger homes
      - Corning, NY (color slides), 1977? (Box 117, Folder 16)
      - Hastings, NY house, undated (Box 117, Folder 17)
      - "Willowlake," Fishkill, NY
        - Construction, 1921-28; undated (Box 117, Folder 1)
        - Exterior, 1924; 1928; 1946; undated (Box 117, Folder 2-4)
        - Interior, undated (Box 117, Folder 5)
        - Surrounding scenery, undated (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - "Casa de Adobe," Tucson, AZ
        - Exterior and interior, 1937; undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
        - Surrounding scenery, undated (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Sierra Vista Drive house, 1949; undated (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Valley House (nursing home), Tucson, AZ, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified scenes, 1897-1948; undated (Box 118, Folder 11-12)
  - Color transparencies and reproductions of various pictures in Sanger Papers, 1898-1932; undated (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Margaret Sanger Papers in the Sophia Smith Collection: images of the selected items and document boxes, 1966; undated (Box 118, Folder 14)
- SERIES X. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  This series contains miscellaneous oversize items from most of the other series, arranged in the same order. The bulk of it consists of awards, honors, and memorabilia. The latter is primarily gifts given to Sanger during her world travels, including Japanese slippers, some scrapbooks, and drawings and sculptures of Sanger.
  - Biographical material
    - Personal records: Passport, 1915 (Box 119)
    - Awards, honors, anniversaries, and honorary degrees
      - Honorary degree hoods: Smith College, 1949 and University of Arizona, 1965 (Box 119)
      - World Tribute to Margaret Sanger1961: Guest book (Box 119)
      - Third Class of the Order of the Precious Crown1965: citation in Japanese (Box 119)
      - Family planning commemorative stamp, 1972 (Box 119)
      - Poem re: M. Sanger by Desire Vail, undated (Box 119)
      - Drawing of M. Sanger's arrest by J. Downs, presented by Today's Health, undated (Box 119)
      - Embroidered hanging from India (unidentified), undated (Box 119)
      - Albert and Mary Lasker Foundation Award1950: Plaster relief of medal (Box 120)
      - Citation in Japanese, Tokyo, 1955 (Box 120)
      - World Tribute to Margaret Sanger, Waldorf-Astoria, New York, NY, May 11-12, 1961, sponsored by the World Population Emergency Campaign: Letters and telegrams, A-Z (2 vols.) (Box 121)
    - Miscellaneous memorabilia
      - Artwork (mostly water colors by M. Sanger), undated (Box 122)
        [see also Flat File]
      - Drawings of Gandhi by Yuping Wong, 1931 and M. Sanger by Samuel Cahan, 1929 (Box 123)
      - Bas-relief of M. Sanger as a nurse by Betty Barstow Long (Box 123)
      - "Men of Affairs," The Evening Mail (cartoons of prominent men, including J. Noah Sleeundated) (Box 124)
  - Organization and conference files
    - International Conference on Planned Parenthood, 6th, Delhi, 1959: Poster, 20 February 1959 (Box 125)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation, "Activities": [Educational materials?], undated (Box 125)
    - Maternity Center Association, New York: Maternity Care in Pictures, 1939 (Box 125)
    - World Population Conference, 1927: Cartoon menu, "Vive le Bebe"; Journal, 2, 2 September 1927; and publications [in Danish?], "compliments of ---- Hansen"] (Box 125)
  - Countries and regions
    - Russia: Mother and Child, published by the Leningrad Branch of the All-Union Society for Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries and the Leningrad Health Department, 1930s (Box 126)
    - Japan: Scrapbook of clippings (also on microfilm) (Box 126)
    - India and other countries: Scrapbook of clippings, 1935-36 (Box 127)
  - Printed material
    - The Birth Control Herald (Voluntary Parenthood League), July 1922-March 1924 (Box 127a)
    - Birth Control News (Society for Constructive Birth Control, London), 1922-29
      - Volume I-II, 1922 to April 1924 (Box 127a)
      - Volume III-VII (incomplete), May 1924 to 1929 (Box 127b)
    - Lucifer the Light-Bearer
      - 5 February 1886-28 August 1891 (Box 128)
      - 4 September 1891-25 December 1896 (Box 129)
    - The Woman Rebel [Incomplete], May; January; September/October 1914 (Box 129)
  - Photographs
    - Mary Higgins (framed portrait) (Box 130)
    - Japan album, 1959 (Box 130)
    - Portraits of M. Sanger
      - 1925-29 (Box 130)
      - 1935 (Box 131)
      - 1940s-50s (Box 131)
  - On shelf: wood boxes with Japanese characters (2)
  - Charcoal drawing of M. Sanger by Lisa Baskin for Margaret Sanger Centennial Conference (Map-case Flat file)
  - Photographs: M. Sanger with J. Noah Slee in Potsdam, circa 1927; Stuart Sanger with Yale class of 1928 (Map-case Flat file)
  - Tucson Title Insurance co. map, undated (Map-case Flat file)
  - Chinese family planning posters (2) (Map-case Flat file)
  - Japanese poster (Map-case Flat file)
  - Poster, "Mrs. Sanger Defends Birth Control" (Morning Post, Hong Kong), undated (Map-case Flat file)
  - 13 watercolors by Margaret Sanger (Map-case Flat file)
- SERIES XI. MICROFILM
  The Microfilm series is intellectually arranged into 5 subseries: Correspondence, Organizational Records/Conference Materials, Legal/Governmental Material, Writings, and Miscellany.
  - SUBSERIES I: CORRESPONDENCE
    - 1900 [start of reel S01] (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1910-12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 4-9)
    - 1915 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - 1916 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1917 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1918 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1919 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1920 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1921
      - January-June (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - July-December [start of reel S02] (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1922 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
    - 1923 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
    - 1924 (Box 2, Folder 6-9)
    - 1925
      - January-March (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - April-December [start of reel S03] (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
    - 1926 (Box 3, Folder 5-8)
    - 1927
      - January-September (Box 3, Folder 9-11)
      - Oct-December [start of reel S04] (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
    - 1928 (Box 4, Folder 1-8)
    - 1929
      - January-March (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - April-September [start of reel S05] (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
      - Oct-December (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
    - 1930 (Box 5, Folder 4-9)
    - 1931
      - January-March [start of reel S06] (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - April-December (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
    - 1932
      - January-March (Box 6, Folder 6-8)
    - April [start of reel S07], 1932 (Box 9)
      - May-December (Box 7, Folder 1-8)
    - 1933
      - January-July (Box 7, Folder 9-12)
      - August-December [start of reel S08] (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
    - 1934
      - January-July (Box 8, Folder 5-11)
      - August-December [start of reel S09] (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
    - 1935
      - January-April (Box 9, Folder 5-8)
      - May-December [start of reel S10] (Box 10, Folder 1-7)
    - 1936
      - January (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - February-Oct [start of reel S11] (Box 11, Folder 1-9)
      - November (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - December [start of reel S12] (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
    - 1937
      - January-March (Box 12, Folder 4-7)
      - April (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - May-Oct [start of reel S13] (Box 13, Folder 2-8)
      - November (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - December [start of reel S14] (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1938
      - January-February (Box 14, Folder 3-6)
      - March-April (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
      - March-April (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
      - May-August [start of reel S15] (Box 15, Folder 4-7)
      - September-November (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
      - December [start of reel S16] (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
    - 1939
      - January-1-15 March (Box 16, Folder 6-9)
      - 19-30 March-June (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
    - July-Oct [start of reel S17], 1939 (Box 5-7)
      - November-December (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - 1940
      - January-May (Box 18, Folder 4-7)
      - June-December [reel S18] (Box 19, Folder 1-7)
    - 1941
      - January-March [start of reel S19] (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
      - April-1-21 July (Box 20, Folder 4-7)
      - 22-31 July-September (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
      - Oct-December [start of reel S20] (Box 21, Folder 4-6)
    - 1942
      - January-March (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
      - April-June [start of reel S21] (Box 22, Folder 4-6)
      - July-December (Box 23, Folder 1-6)
    - 1943
      - January-June [start of reel S22] (Box 24, Folder 1-6)
      - July 1-5 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - 7-31 July-December [start of reel S23] (Box 25, Folder 2-7)
      - undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - 1944
      - January [start of reel S23] (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - February-June [continues on reel S23 through to reel S24] (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
      - July-November (Box 26, Folder 5-9)
      - December (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - 1945
      - January-August (Box 27, Folder 2-5)
      - September-December [start of reel S25] (Box 27, Folder 6-8)
    - =, 1946 (Box 27)
      - January-July (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
      - August-November [start of reel S26] (Box 28, Folder 6-9)
      - December (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 1947
      - January-May [continues on reel S26 through to reel S27] (Box 29, Folder 2-4)
      - June-Oct (Box 29, Folder 5-9)
      - November-December (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 1948
      - January-February (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - March-July [start of reel S28] (Box 30, Folder 4-7)
      - August-Oct (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
      - November-December [start of reel S29] (Box 31, Folder 4-6)
    - 1949
      - January-April (Box 32, Folder 1-4)
      - May-June [start of reel S30] (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - July-December, undated (Box 33, Folder 1-7)
    - 1950
      - January-August (Box 34, Folder 1-7)
      - September-December, undated (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
    - 1951 (Box 35)
      - January-February (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
      - March-July [reel S34] (Box 36, Folder 1-5)
      - August-December [reel S35] (Box 37, Folder 1-6)
    - 1952
      - January-March [reel S36] (Box 38, Folder 1-6)
      - April-15 June [reel S37] (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
      - 16 June-16 July [start of reel S38] (Box 40, Folder 1-6)
      - 17 July-10 September [continues onto reel S38 through to reel S39] (Box 41, Folder 1-6)
      - 11 September-December, undated [continues onto reel S39 through to reel S40] (Box 42, Folder 1-5)
    - 1953
      - 1-18 January (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - 19 January-May [start of reel S40 through to reel S41] (Box 43, Folder 1-6)
      - June-December, undated [continues onto reel S41 through to reel S42] (Box 44, Folder 1-5)
    - 1954
      - 1-19 January (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - 20 January-March [continues onto reel S43] (Box 45, Folder 1-6)
      - April-10 August [continues onto reel S44] (Box 46, Folder 1-6)
      - 11 August-19 November [continues onto reel S44 through to reel S45] (Box 47, Folder 1-6)
      - 20 November-December, undated (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
    - 1955
      - January-February [continues onto reel S45 through to reel S46] (Box 48, Folder 4-6)
      - March-April [continues onto reel S46 through to reel S47] (Box 49, Folder 1-4)
      - May-26 July [continues onto reel S47 through to reel S48] (Box 50, Folder 1-5)
      - 27 July-November (Box 51, Folder 1-6)
      - December (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - 1956
      - January-15 April [start of reel S49] (Box 52, Folder 2-6)
      - 16 April-16 August [continues onto reel S49 through to reel S50] (Box 53, Folder 1-6)
      - 17 August-December (Box 54, Folder 1-5)
    - 1957
      - January [start of reel S51] (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - February-11 June [continues onto reel S51 through to reel S52] (Box 55, Folder 1-8)
      - 12 June-9 Oct (Box 56, Folder 1-6)
      - 10 Oct-December [continues onto reel S52 through to reel S53] (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
    - 1958
      - January-13 March (Box 57, Folder 4-6)
      - 14 March-August [continues onto reel S53 through to reel S54] (Box 58, Folder 1-6)
      - September-December (Box 59, Folder 1-5)
    - 1959
      - January-August [start of reel S55] (Box 60, Folder 1-8)
      - September-December [continues onto reel S55 through to reel S56] (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
    - 1960
      - January (Box 61, Folder 5-6)